The Filmmakers' Commemorative Edition
9/11 is a documentary, tv movie film directed by James Hanlon.
An on-the-scene documentary following the events of September 11, 2001 from an insider's view, through the lens of two French filmmakers who
simply set out to make a movie about a rookie NYC fireman and ended up filming the tragic event that changed our lives forever.
Self, played by Tony Benatatos.
Self, played by Jamal Braithwaite.
Self, played by Joseph Casaliggi.
Self, played by James Hanlon.
Self, played by Joseph Pfeifer.
Self, played by Tom Spinard.
9/11 is a 2002 documentary film about the September 11 attacks in New York City, in which two planes were flown into the
buildings of the World Trade Center, resulting in their destruction and the deaths of nearly 3,000 people.
The film premiered on CBS on March 10, 2002.
The film is from the point of view of the New York City Fire Department.
The film was directed by brothers Jules and Gédéon Naudet and FDNY
firefighter James Hanlon and produced by Susan Zirinsky of CBS News.
The film explores themes of war on terror, 9/11, firefighter,
observational documentary, documentary film.